Hello friends, today I am
sharing with you
HDV Financial Services. This is a
multinational company. It is a financial
company. Similarly, ICICI Bank. You must have heard of
ICICI Bank.
We are an insurance
company. Both are
two big companies in India. Its vacancies are.
I am sharing with you.
ICICI Bank is in our
Kerala. Kannur is in Kota.
Thrissur is in our Kerala. You can apply.
But
I did not see any vacancy in HDBI. It is in
Chennai. Coimbatore is in
Bangalore. So I have written here.
I saw Chennai, Bangalore, Coimbatore. So
you can apply there.
Apart from that, you do not have to go there to apply.
You have been given their email ID and mobile
number. Who should you contact? Who should you
send the application to? The rest of the interviews for both companies are going on.
Apart from that,
direct hiring is also going on.  There is
no application fee and
you don't have any exam.
You
send your resume to someone's email.
Then they will call you. If you are like that,
they will
say that sometimes it will be an online
interview. Sometimes they will
call you for the final. So,
those are the
things that I am
sharing with you today. If you are new to my
video, you should
subscribe. Similarly, if
you liked the video,
you should like or comment. Let's move on to the
rest of it.
Then,
one is from HDFE Financial Services. Apart from that, ICICI Lombard and ICICI
Lombard. You know, ICICI Lombard. They have
all
kinds of insurance for us. So, I am
sharing with you the things of two companies that are growing very well. So, let's
move on to those things.
I have already said an important thing in this. There is no
exam fee for you.
Similarly, there is
no exam for you. Similarly, in both of these,
people who are under pressure can also
apply.  You must
be a graduate.
I found that there are vacancies for 12th graders at HDB
.  But if we were to say one thing
in common between the two, we would be
asking about those who have graduated.  Okay,
let's get into those things.
So, for the first time, let me tell you about ICICI Bank.
We are applying through Naukari.com
.  Here it says
Unit Sales Manager,
where is it located? Kannur
is there, Kottayam is there, Thrissur is there.  Here
you can see Kannur, Kottayam, Thrissur,
this is
not a direct interview, backing interview, you have to
apply. Now let's see
how to apply.
What is this qualification for you? It
says here, zero to four years. You
can apply for pressure within this.
Here, what is your salary? 1.75
lakh to 4.25 tafa. Each of you, what is your
appearance, what is your
qualification, what is your experience?
Depending on those things, you can
change it. Kannur has
Kottayam, Thrissur has
said here, this is field sales. Your
work here, let's
first understand this at a glance.
Field sales is general insurance, it is
agency channel. All the things are
said here. How can we
apply here? Here, we click and
go to this page of Appanakkari.com. So, if
you
have not registered here before, you should do it.   The
unit sales manager has.
You can also click here to see the
job highlights
.  They published this vacancy a week ago. There
are 10 openings, out of which 13 people
have already applied. You should apply.
It's not a big deal considering we have 13 or more people doing it.
Our one goal is to do everything, that is,
every thing they ask, we are
graduates, we are graduates,
or we have experience, but even if we have all this, for
some reason we are unlucky
because we did not
get a job from it, so if you are disappointed, let
us move forward in one thing, this is not about this
one job, no matter what, if
we are
disappointed, let us move forward
quickly, we cannot see the highlight here. The highlight here is that
you must have a minimum of six months of field sales experience
and you must
be a graduate. The bread that is said here is that
you have only five days of work in
a week. The job match score
says that you are an early applicant. The
job
description says that you are a job
profile that says sales of health
policies through agent in assigned territory. The job description
says that you are an agent in assigned territory. So when you
come here,
you apply here after that.   If
you are applying here,
click on this link to apply here
.  So here I am registering this and
showing my name here.  If you are
not registered, you will get
an option to register here and
there you need to register.  So
here I am asking you for example
what is your current CTC what is your current salary and
so on I wrote 7 lakhs
for example 7 lakhs
I wrote 5 lakhs I have 5 lakhs I
don't know I don't have a salary I don't have
a salary I wrote 5 lakhs
Then when this is saved here
you can go ahead and
write 5 lakhs You can write this if you do
n't have a salary now
or if you don't want to write just show Skip Question Skip this Question Let's
go to the next
thing Humas of Experience You in
Field Sales Field Sales If
you have experience you should
write or you should save here you
can't skip here If you are no you should write no
So in this way you just have to go ahead and
apply The thing I quickly
showed you more things
By registering me
they will take every thing by default Then
I will tell you more things  It
doesn't matter, you can go inside and I'll give you the
link below. You don't have to comment on yesterday's calculation.
I'll give you both the ICISA and HDHDV in the description below my video.
You can click there and
go directly and apply.
Or if you have any
problem from there, if you definitely
write something like "link please" or "link",
only one person will like you yesterday. Like, like, like, or no like, it will
only write "high".   And then I
know that I am
doing it for Link.
So if you leave a
comment there, I might give you the link
.
Maybe I can give you the link if you don't need it.   Apart
from that, there is one important thing:
you don't need
to request a separate link to make this video your own.  It's
good for me to comment on the link you want, it's
good for me, it'll
increase my reach for the video.  But I'm saying
you don't have to do that
.  You
can see what I am giving to many people in the comment box of the video. From there,
you
can click and go directly and apply.
If not, it is good for you to comment. It is good for me.
You will get
direct.
I said that at one time to reduce it.
So after this, there are
other vacancies here. Let's see
what the vacancies are again. You can
apply like this.
But the rest of
us have these three vacancies in Kerala. There are not
many vacancies.
Customer Relationship Manager is in Mumbai. If
there is anyone in Mumbai,
you should apply. You know, when we
say hybrid job, you don't get it
wrong. If we
say hybrid job, we do it in the office and also at
home. We have both. We have
work from home and work from
office. Apart from that, if we
say hybrid, we
do both together. If you
all know, I have just
shared a little knowledge of mine with you.
So, the next thing we have to go to is
HDV.
I have provided a link to the HDV vacancy.
I'll write two of them separately for you and
give you a link.  You just need to click on it
.
You can apply for the position within the Urgent Opening for Pressure mentioned here
.  There is an urgent
opening in Bangalore, and its Bangalore location
is being shown.  What you're saying here is zero to one
year.  This means that
people who are very important to you
can apply within this.  And when
this is over, you will
come to this place in Bangalore.  But
this turned out to be a walking interview.  It's from November 26th to
December 26th.  You should
prepare your CV directly and
open it here to see
what it says.  If you
want to change jobs by creating your CV in that way,
you have plenty of time to do the remaining interviews from November 26th
to December
.  There are still days.   If
you have time at any time,
you can definitely attend the rest of this
interview
.  When he comes, the rest is in
Chennai, for those of you in Chennai,
I have only seen one interview,
the rest you need to apply for, I have given
you here.  That is,
you can apply their email ID here and
click and apply.
Or you
can send them to your email ID in a very simple way. Now,
I am urgently hiring for EMI Process
Executive. It is said here that EMI of the bank is being
collected. All
its matters are
in Chennai. This vacancy is in
Chennai. When you come here,
you can contact this number that says "Contact Google" here. If you want to
apply for all that, I
have given you a link to apply.  You
can apply through that.
This is a good vacancy for those who are interested to apply
.  Both are good companies.   It's a
good thing if you get it.  Okay,
best of luck to all of you.